Se-no, GALGAL-chan go-go!
Yes, so this time the two of us will be playing Sakura Moppan!
What kind of moppan? I think this might be my first Moppan show!
Moppan...maybe my first Moppan!
A・M・S・M・R
I've never done A・S・M・R.
I've never done A・S・M・R, so I've never done A・S・M・R.
I've never done A, S, M, and R before.
I've bought a lot of these spring limited editions, so we're going to eat them together.
I'm new to this kind of thing, so I don't know how it's going to go
I'm a little nervous.
I'm curious about the puddings.
Do you want me to introduce them one at a time?
Once...
Sakura Monaka.
Oh, it's a monaka?
Sakura Kaoru Pie.
I can't see what's inside. What is it?
But you like pies, right? What flavor?
What flavor? It's got bean paste. It's got Sakura bean paste.
Sakura milk pudding
Milk pudding. Pudding pudding.
I just heard about it.
Sakura and Uji green tea.
Uji green tea. Perfect.
Sounds delicious.
I love matcha, right?
Sakura cake, Sakura mochi!
Sakura doughnut with Sakura rice cake, fluffy rice cake roll, sweet bean paste and Sakura whip!
Looks good! It's got some kind of red bean paste in it!
Can I eat this? Bon appétit!
Delicious. I've never had something like this before. It's so Japanese.
We just talked about going to see the cherry blossoms.
We were just talking about going to see the cherry blossoms.
We've never been together to see cherry blossoms.
I think we should go see cherry blossoms together. A picnic.
But I wonder if hay fever is a big deal... hay fever, right?
We even sneezed on each other at the release event.
That's true. Hay fever kids are a different story.
I'll miss Osechi at home.
Osechi? Osechi is for New Year's.
Then what do they eat?
It's a picnic, so we made everything for lunch.
Sandwiches...
Yeah, well, there's really no rules.
I think I'll bring some strawberries for the eight-day killer.
Great.
He's bringing strawberries, isn't he? I like strawberries.
Can I have some?
I'll have a sakura mochi.
I'll have a sakura rice cake. I like the smell of sakura.
Look at this too. Can I eat it? Sakura sweets.
Is this your first time? I'm going to eat it like this.
Here's a note.
It's my first time. Here.
Can you see it?
Like this?
Do you eat cherry blossoms like this?
Or cherry blossoms you pick up?
Aren't they dangerous?
They're preserved in salt, too.
It's wrapped.
It's the first time I've seen cherry blossoms.
It's true... sometimes they have flowers on them.
The pie is delicious!
The pie is too good!
The pie is too good
What should I bring to Hanami?
How about a sandwich?
But maybe Yuzu will make something sweet.
Sure, Yuzu could do the sucking.
Maybe an omu-rice?
Bring a big omelet with rice.
Something like this for a picnic.
Picnic size.
Pow!
Wow, I'd go up if we had omelette rice.
I'm making lunch.
I'm making lunch for eight people.
There are 8 lunches.
But we're like the Ogawa family.
That's how the Ogawa family is.
We're a family of 8. That's right. We talk about it a lot.
You know that omelette you use for a casserole?
You know that pot you use to make omelette rice?
Then you put the eggs in like this.
I don't know if it's common for Sunny's family to make omelette rice in a frying pan.
I heard it's hard to even hold the frying pan like this, so I guess so... fried rice is very hard, because it turns into fried rice.
Mochi rice cakes. Mochi rice cakes...
You're such a beginner! Like this... I'll study it in the video.
It's not a parfait, it's a pudding. It's got red bean paste in it.
I don't usually eat red bean paste. Yeah, you don't usually eat them.
Yeah, I don't eat them at all. That's why it's so rare today.
Here you go.
Sweet. The cream is really sweet, but the pudding is really good.
I don't have a sweet tooth. I ate the whole thing. It's really good.
It's already been hyped up, so it's easy to eat even if you don't like anko (sweet bean paste).
Haru, Haru. You're turning 20, right?
I forgot... that's right! I'm turning 20!
Congratulations!
Minami's taking me to a theme park...
Last year, when I turned 19, it was a present for my 19th birthday
I'm turning 20.
Don't go in May. Don't take me there.
March.
We talked about going when it was warmer, but it got cold.
We'll do May in a hurry.
Yoka took me there two years ago.
When you turned 16?
Two years ago, I think.
Two years ago. -Two years ago. Two years ago.
It's open.
Oh, my God, it's a parfait. It's too much!
Panpinky?
Yo-kasan, it's too sweet!
Want to try some at Machan's? My stomach is growling.
But when this video was uploaded...
Yohka's an adult. She's 20 now.
What really surprised me was...
She's 18?
She's turning 20 so fast.
You've already turned 20, I remember having fun at 18 or 19?
I graduated from high school.
It all happened so fast? Yeah.
But every year it seems like it goes by faster and faster.
Yeah, but it's already gone so fast.
When I'm a grandma, I'll probably finish a year in a week.
Too fast, too fast.
It's been about a week. I thought it'd be about a week, but it's probably already...
Maybe December.
But I'm also scared that it's already April, and we've got two months till the concert.
We're working hard to get things going, so I hope you're looking forward to it!
I'm going to eat them with the members who love sweets.
Thank you for watching!
If you think it looks delicious or you want to try it, please give it a high rating, subscribe to our channel, and leave a comment!
Congratulations to Yokachan!
We look forward to seeing you soon!
Bye bye!
This time I'm wearing a costume by D-Holic!